Hey everybody, we are joined by the
Packers director of college scouting
Matt Malaspina. Matt, thanks for the
time and welcome. And folks, we're lucky
because Matt is a former offensive
lineman. He really knows these offensive
lineman. Tell me about Jager Burton,
center guard type guy you drafted out of
Kentucky in the fifth round. Well, we're
very excited to have him.
Uh I am
very excited about his future and and
what he's going to be for this team.
Started at guard there, started at
center,
uh fifth-year player, so he went through
the process to develop.
>> [music]
>> Big, strong, athletic, tough, smart,
check, check, check, check, you know,
everything we're looking for.
You're talking about a young man with 47
starts
at the highest level of college
football. What does that do for him?
I think initially they feel comfortable.
You know, they're not walking in
starstruck as they played on the biggest
stages of LSU, Alabama, Georgia, and at
a high level. So, it's it's it's an
adjustment for every player, but you're
taking a lot of the learning curve out
of it because of the standard that
they've had to perform to. Now, I
haven't seen the mountain of tape you've
seen on this young man,
but I've seen enough. You know what? I
look at him and said, "That kid knows
what he's doing."
>> Oh, yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, he's uh
he's very comfortable, you know, there's
no panic to his game.
Um he's a smart, very smart, graduated
with a high GPA. I was telling the guys
in there before, an accomplished chess
player, ambidextrous, which is kind of
unique. Um
but uh
just
what we're looking for.
Matt, how do you feel Jager fitting into
the mix? And you know, we're when they
start lining them up and it'll be next
weekend, they start lining How do you
see him fitting in? Where?
I would say center or guard really cuz
he's played both. So, wherever the
coaches want to train him initially, but
he's a guy you can stick in at practice
at guard, you can stick him in at
center. It's where you need him really,
and he's comfortable at both [music] and
he's played both and played both at a
high level. This is kind of an
interesting quality
during your press conference [music]
discussing Jager. You said he always
does his job. And that's kind of job one
as an offensive lineman, consistency.
>> when they say your name it's a bad
thing.
No, he he does his job and and he's very
comfortable doing. He's very well
coached. I was telling the guys in there
before, Eric Wolford who's now at LSU is
an outstanding offensive line coach. He
and I worked together in San Fran.
Uh he was his coach his freshman year,
his junior and senior year uh cuz Wolfie
went to Bama for a for a minute there,
but um he's
trained at a high level. Expectations
were very high in that room, and you
know, from mental toughness to physical
toughness to the practice habits, he's
seen it all, you know, and so here we
go. Now, come up here and and give it a
shot here.